A child cannot consent to
a surrogacy arrangement.
Shivani Raja MP
Conservative · Leicester East
They cannot understand the
promises adults have made.
We must also speak
for the child who
Dr Neil Shastri-Hurst MP
Conservative · Solihull West and Shirley
cannot speak for
his or herself,
and protect the
woman who carries
and gives birth to that child.
Pregnant women
are not factories.
Jonathan Hinder MP
Labour · Pendle and Clitheroe
Babies are not
goods to be ordered.
There are things in our
society, Mr Pritchard,
Steve Yemm MP
Labour · Mansfield
which I believe should never
be reduced to questions
around contract and individual
choice or intention.
And I'm certain that
motherhood is one of those.
Compensation for
genuine expenses
Jim Shannon MP
DUP · Strangford
of carrying a
baby is one thing.
Paying a woman for carrying
a baby is quite another.
50% of responses to the Law
Commission's consultation
Tracy Gilbert MP
Labour · Edinburgh North and Leith
called for a total ban
on surrogacy in the UK.
I fully support that ban.